Hello friends, you are
very welcome to Trading Deck. Friends, in this video
we are going to talk about the stock
ICICI Lombard General Insurance and
I have put its monthly timeframe chart.
First of all, if you guys see, the
stock is trending around 11:30 hundred rupees
and the
stock is trading around the important zone. Friends, it was a one-
time support stock. If you
guys see it previously, then this is an all-time support. If I
tell you exactly, then I will
show you its data by analyzing it. After that,
I will also tell you what position can be made in the current market price.
And for those who have the stock, I will
give preference to feminine star plus. Friends, the
video is going to be a very informative video till the end. There is
no stop four times. This
support has been taken from around this important support. And I feel that
friends, the
market does not usually take important supports
because the ICICI Lombard General  The
stock is 11:30, which means it has such a low
valuation that if it breaks down the support, then
which is the direct top near it,
friends, the lever of ₹850, ₹800 and such a
huge fall, I don't think
this stock will show any stop because it was
already this much and the valuation is also the
fundamental truth of the stock, so it seems to me that
taking support from around this level, the
stock should continue its upward momentum,
now if you people
see how to find out the reversals here, the
people who
have the stock here, then till what level would I give
preference to the people to place stop loss,
friends, my dream
because there is also a ground number of ₹1000 and
if 98 stocks go below ₹2000,
then we have to get out of it, friends,
because what is our entire lap in the
market, there is stop loss, so
you people have to stop there
around 999, plan about your Star Plus  I am
doing this and if we talk about the upper side then
friends I
see the stock going up to near 1880 rupees
friends it will take a little longer we will also see it
together but I see this stock
going up to that point if I tell you guys about
multiple party stocks then which could be its
important targets
after the stock goes up to that point you can see some
pressure or something or the other it can
also show a little bit of a reversal first of all if you
guys see where your entry point is going to be
friends you get to see a little more selling
pressure so
around 11:30 you should place 1130 and some of your
entry points within this a stop
loss of 900 means I am planning a stoppage of 12% from here
and the
target is going to be as per the investment opportunity friends its
first target is going to be ₹1300 where I will
book a little quantity
after that its second target is going to be 1417
and talking about the final target then
Simply put, you can see this stock going up to 1500 or even 1480
and if any important
moment comes in it, then I will share four parts of that too with
you guys, friends,
after that I bring this type of live video on
my channel daily, what
more can you guys learn, you can understand how to
find out patterns,
how important
behavior comes inside the stop and through the shot, I also provide you guys an
overview of Early Morning NIFT
with Star Plus entry point target point along with the
region, friends, for this type of knowledge,
you guys subscribe to the channel for live content,
see you in the next video,
Jai Hind